soulstrut.com 2011-06-06

# Today's DJ, Musician, and Collector | Soul Strut

## Privacy Policy

UPDATED June 1, 2010

Your privacy is critically important to us. At Soul Strut we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:

( **Soul Strut** ) operates Soul Strut.com. It is Soul Strut’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

**WEBSITE VISITORS**

Like most website operators, Soul Strut collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Soul Strut’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Soul Strut’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Soul Strut may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Soul Strut also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Soul Strut does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

**GATHERING OF PERSONALLY-IDENTIFYING INFORMATION**

Certain visitors to Soul Struts websites choose to interact with Soul Strut in ways that require Soul Strut to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Soul Strut gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up account at Soulstrut.com to provide a username and email address. Soul Strut collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitors interaction with Soul Strut. Soul Strut does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**AGGREGATED STATISTICS**

Soul Strut may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Soul Strut may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Soul Strut does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

**PROTECTION OF CERTAIN PERSONALLY-IDENTIFYING INFORMATION**

Soul Strut discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Soul Struts behalf or to provide services available at Soul Struts websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Soul Struts websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Soul Strut will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Soul Strut discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Soul Strut believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Soul Strut, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Soul Strut website and have supplied your email address, Soul Strut may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with whats going on with Soul Strut and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Soul Strut takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

**COOKIES**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitors computer, and that the visitors browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Soul Strut uses cookies to help Soul Strut identify and track visitors, their usage of Soul Strut website, and their website access preferences. Soul Strut visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Soul Struts websites, with the drawback that certain features of Soul Struts websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Soul Strut may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Soul Struts sole discretion. Soul Strut encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

This Privacy Policy was derived from Wordpress’s version which is available under a Creative Commons Sharealike license.
